Black Hook Strikes Back
What's all this?
All of these are my inventions.
Buster Gallon, self proclaimed genius inventor on planet Machina.
You could have left out the "self proclaimed" part...
Is this a pen?
That is a cheat pen that will automatically write the correct answers for you.
With this I could be the top of the cl-
Auckpth!
It's actually a pen that punishes those who would try to cheat with it.
And... what's this?
It's a brush that makes your hair beautiful with just one stroke.
Wow, really?
See? Beautiful, isn't it?
These inventions are all pretty silly...
But aren't they fun?
What do you mean?
What's so fun about this?!
To me, it's the most fun to see the ridiculous look on people's faces after they've been tricked!
Really? That's what you find "fun"?
Are we sure we should accept this prankster as our teammate?
No way! Can trust him as far as you can throw him!
I have to agree.
I don't trust him either.
No... But he... oh...
I trust him!
What?!
Jun?!
Why not? He's so fun!
I enjoy a good prank too, you know!
I think you're being too trusting.
You'll regret it if you end up getting stabbed in the back. But by then, it'll be too late.
But... if you keep expecting the worst of someone, you'll never build any trust!
I'll trust you. Jun.
Great!
Then that means you can trust me in that we can trust Buster Gallon!
What does that even mean?
Anyway! Welcome to the team! It's great to have you, Buster Gallon!
Hm?
What's going on?
What's wrong?
Is it a power outage?
What's going on?
What's happening?
This doesn't seem like a simple blackout.
The current dropped, but it hasn't stopped completely.
Do you think there could be a problem at the power plant?
Huh? Daddy?! Is that true?!
What is it, Anna?
A strange ship has appeared at Mowtown's electrical facility!
What?! Is it...
It's Black Hook!
Hahahaha! Give me everything you've got!
Aah! At this rate, the entire city will be shut down!
Hurry! We gotta stop him!
Got it!
Black Hook...
Everyone, take back!
I wonder... what is he trying to do by attacking the electrical facility?
Black Hook is trying to absorb all of the electricity to power himself up!
Trying to take in all of that energy at once... Typical of Black Hook!
That sure is one greedy pirate.
He was already strong in the first place! We'll never beat him if he absorbs all that power.
Theo! Anna! I have an idea!
Yahaha!
Still not enough! More! MORE!
Anyone who interrupts my meal will be crushed!
Huh?
What?!
Water Splash!
Let's go! Mega Ambler!
Mega Ambler, Forceps Shock!
Forceps Shock!
Hyeeaagh!
We did it!
The water conducted electricity, just as Jun planned!
Augh, my car...
Don't get smart with me, you punks!!
Guys, come back!
Ha! Did you really think that little plan of yours would be enough to stop me?
Then how about this?
Fleta Z!
Fleta Z, setup!
Fleta Z, Beak Arrow!
Beak Arrow!
Heh! This puny arrow is nothing to me!
Now, Fleta Z!
Right!
Why isn't it coming out?! W-What?
I'm losing energy!
Haven't you ever heard of a grounding conductor?
It's a safety device that sends excess electricity from washing machines and refrigerators into the ground!
Now all the energy you absorbed will be sent back into the ground!
You did it!
That's our Jun!
My car!
It's all thanks to you guys!
Why, you little...
How 'bout I share some with you?
Fleta Z, come back!
You brats are starting to get on my nerves!
It's about time you've been punished!
Mega Trucker, setup!
Shoulder Shield!
How long do you think you can keep that up?!
Mega Trucker can't handle this on his own!
Right. We all have to work together!
Alright. Let's do it!
We all got your back!
Oh! We haven't done this move in a while!
Buffalo Crush! Buster Gallon!
You guys will help too, right?
I guess we don't have a choice.
Buffalo Crush will help you!
And here we have the two shameless traitors.
You sold your souls to that Earthling runt, and now you dare to strike me down?!
Me Buffalo Crush... never sold soul to anyone!
What'd you say?!
Planet Machina gone.
We have to live on Earth now.
You. Me. Everyone!
Stop talking!
Oh no!
After exerting all of that energy, he still has the strength to charge his finishing blow?!
Everyone, concentrate on the shield!
Bring it on!
No! There's no time!
Grand... Captain's Cannon!
Oh my. I've never been one to lose my cool,
and here I almost ended up destroying the Metal Breath.
Oh no... Everyone? Pull yourselves together!
Now, you are the only ones left.
Run away, Jun!
I can't do that!
Never... I will never run and leave my friends behind!
Ever!
That light...?
Could it be? The light of the forbidden power?!
Forbidden... power?
A legendary force from planet Machina!
So powerful that it had to be sealed away!
I should have known... it existed within the Metal Breath!
Small fry!
Give it to me right now! Hand it over!
I-I don't know what any of that is!
But I will never let you have it!
What is he doing?!
Buster Gallon... You?!
Here you go.
It's all yours now... Captain.
He's kidding, right?!
Did he just betray us?!
This can't be!...
Well done, Buster Gallon!
You... I knew I could always put my trust in you!
With this, the universe will be ours! Hahaha!
What did I tell you?! I knew we shouldn't have taken him in!
I believe I told you.
It is my greatest joy to see the ridiculous look on your faces...
...after you've been tricked.
Yeah!
This is our last chance!
Ack! What is this?!
I can't see anything!
Now's our chance, Buster Gallon!
I'm on it!
My energy! After all of this!!
Buster Gallon, setup!
Thank you for believing in me, Captain.
Buster Gallon! Twin Vulcan!
Twin Vulcan!
Buster Blaster!
Who would have thought I'd be betrayed twice!
I must've lost my edge. I don't deserve to be called Captain...!
Jun!
Blue Cop!
Infinity...
Force...
Break!!
This is it!
Metal Cardbot, Change Up!
Black Hook, sealed!
It's over...
You did it, Jun!
For a moment, I thought we were done for...
Hey you, Buster Gallon. Just who's side are you on?
What do you mean, "who's side"?
Don't act like you don't know.
Were you really thinking of betraying us?
I'm not so sure myself. However...
However?
Jun believed in me.
So I started thinking about believing in him too.
Buster Gallon!
Glad to have you on the team!
The pleasure is mine.
Agh!! My arm!!
Jun! Are you alright?!
Ehehehe! I got you good! Haha!
Oh, my... you got me this time.
Ugh... really, Jun?
You still have the energy for pranks?
Oh... what do I tell the insurance company about this?
Maybe that you made a supreme sacrifice to protect the peace of Mowtown!
That's not gonna work!
It's my dad.
Hello?
What's going on, Daddy?
Anna, where are you right now? Are you okay?
I'm calling because something strange is happening at the landfill.
Look there! A giant mass of ore has just begun to rise out of Landfill 30!
This dome-shaped structure looks large enough to cover the entire landfill!
Should we consider this mysterious phenomenon to be a simple act of nature?!
What is that...?